<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RoomMate</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="terms">
     Our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy have been recently updated.To continue using our app,Please review and agree to our updated terms
    </string>
    <string name="show_dialog">Show dialog</string>
    <string name="show_custom_dialog">Show custom dialog</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="def">In these Terms of Service (“Terms”) the following words and expressions shall have the following meanings unless the context otherwise requires: "Actual Rental Period" The period during which the Guest actually has use of the Property, whether greater or lesser than the Agreed Rental Period; "Advertisement" Any advertisement, regardless its content or form, advertising a Property for rent on a Website; "Agreed Rental Period" The period of time during which the Guest will have use of the Property as agreed between the Host of a Property and the Guest; "Housekeeping Services" Any Housekeeping or additional services which may be provided or arranged by us from time to time, including cleaning, checking out and in of properties and supply of provisions for Guests; "Application" The Roommate online platform and all its related services; "Roommate Account" An account with us created by you or on your behalf by a person acting with your knowledge and consent; "Roommate Content" All content that Roommate makes available through the Website, Application, or Services, including any Content licensed from a third party, but excluding member Content; "Property" Residential ; "Content" Text, graphics, images, music, software (excluding the Application), audio, video, information and any other content or materials of the Website; "Rent"/"Rental Fees" Charges payable by a Guest to a Host for the rent of a property, in the amount displayed in an Advertisement for that property or as otherwise agreed between the host of the Property and the Guest of the Property; "Guest" Any person who agrees with a Host to rent a Property using the Services; "Service Charges" Commissions payable to us by a Host and/or by a Guest for a successful booking.; "Member Content" All Content that a Member posts, uploads, publishes, submits or transmits to be made available through the Services; "Member" A person who completes our account registration process, including a Host, Potential Guest, and Guest; "Host" Any person who owns a Property, or represents the host, which he or she wishes to rent out using the Services; "Potential Guest" Any person who wishes to rent a Property using the Services; "Security Deposit" As defined in paragraph ; "Service Fees" As defined in paragraph ; "Services" The provision of an online platform enabling Hosts to advertise Properties for rent, Hosts and Potential Guests to make arrangements (including payment arrangements) in relation to the rent of those Properties, and for related purposes including arranging Housekeeping Services; "Social Network Site" As defined in paragraph 4.4; "Tax" Taxes and duties of any description in any jurisdiction, in the Union of India including but not limited to income tax, capital gains tax, inheritance tax, corporation tax, goods and service tax, excise duties, and import duties; "Third Party Account" An account with a Social Network Site; "TPA Content" As defined in paragraph 4.7; "Website" https://roommate.techmihirnaik.in/ or any other website through which we make the Services available from time to time; "You" Any person accessing or using the Services, whether as a Host, Potential Guest, Guest or otherwise.

Section and paragraph headings shall not affect the interpretation of these Terms, they are merely there.

A person includes a natural person, corporate or unincorporated body (whether or not having separate legal personality) and that persons legal and personal representatives, successors and permitted assigns.

A reference to a company shall include any company, corporation or other body corporate, wherever and however incorporated or established.

Words in the singular shall include the plural and vice versa.

A reference to one gender shall include a reference to the other genders.

The Terms and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with it shall be governed by the laws of Union of India and the competent court of Ahmedabad has exclusive jurisdiction to settle any such dispute or claim.

A reference to a statute, statutory provision or subordinated legislation is a reference to it as it is in force from time to time, taking account of any amendment or re-enactment and includes any statute, statutory provision or any other type of legislation which it amends or re-enacts.

Any obligation under these Terms on a person not to do something includes an obligation not to agree or allow such thing to be done.

A reference to a document is a reference to that document as varied or replaced (in each case, other than in breach of these Terms) at any time.

Any phrase introduced by the terms "including", "include", "in particular" or any similar expression shall be construed as illustrative and shall not limit the sense of the words preceding those terms.</string>
    <string name="applicable">
        Certain areas of the Services (and your access to or use of certain aspects of the Services or Collective Content) may have different terms and conditions posted or may require you to agree with and accept additional terms and conditions. If there is a conflict between these Terms and terms and conditions posted for a specific area and/or part of the Services, the latter terms and conditions will take precedence with respect to your use of or access to that area of the Services.

You acknowledge and agree that, by accessing or using the Services or by downloading or posting any content from or on the Services you are indicating that you have read, and that you understand and agree to be bound by these Terms, whether or not you have registered with us. If you do not agree to these Terms, then you have no right to access or use the Services.

If you accept or agree to these Terms on behalf of a company or any other legal entity, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to bind that company or other legal entity to these Terms and, in such event, “you” and “your” will refer and apply to that company or other legal entity.

If one or more of the provisions of these Terms are invalid or set aside, the remaining provisions of the Terms shall remain applicable in full.
    </string>
    <string name="about">
        The Services enable Hosts to advertise Properties they wish to rent out and Potential Guests to make arrangements with Hosts to Rent those Properties. The Services also enable Hosts and Guests to make arrangements in relation to Housekeeping Services. We do not own or rent out any Properties ourselves nor do we provide Housekeeping Services ourselves.

You agree that you will only make a claim in relation to the acts or omissions of a Member or third party (including a provider of Housekeeping Services), including in relation to any breach of contract, against that Member or third party and not against us. You will communicate directly with other Members via the Services regarding any Advertisements or bookings of Properties made by you. This paragraph does not affect the right of a Host to make a claim against us in relation to any payment due busy to that Host following receipt by us on behalf of that Host of a payment from a Guest.

In order to create an Advertisement or to obtain a property on rent, you must first register and create an account on https://roommate.techmihirnaik.in/ (see paragraph 4 below).

We have no control over the Content of any Advertisement nor do we check or warrant whether a Property is as described in an Advertisement nor whether a Property described in an Advertisement is in any particular condition.

We are not a party to any arrangements or agreements entered into between Hosts and Potential Guests, Hosts and Guests, or Host or Guests and providers of Housekeeping Services nor are we in any way liable for any claim and/or damages under any such arrangements or agreements.

We do not endorse, certify, recommend, warrant, or guarantee any Members, Properties, or providers of Housekeeping Services. We obtain evidence of identity and address for all Members but we do not guarantee the identity or address or existence or sufficiency of qualifications of any Member nor the accuracy of any other information supplied by any Member or provider of Housekeeping Services. You are solely responsible for determining the identity and suitability of others who you contact via the Services. Except as expressly provided in these Terms, we will not be responsible and/or liable for any damage or harm resulting from or arising in connection with your use of the Services or any contact or dealings you may have with other Members or providers of Housekeeping Services.

We have no authority to act for, or enter into contracts or other binding obligations on behalf of Hosts, Potential Guests, Guests or providers of Housekeeping Services. We have no control over, and shall have no responsibility for, nor shall we be in any way be liable for the acts or omissions of any Hosts, Potential Guests, Guests or providers of Housekeeping Services.
    </string>
    <string name="account">
        In order to access certain features of the Services, rent a property or create an Advertisement, you must register to create a Roommate Account and become a Member. You may register directly via the Services or as described in this section.

We will create your Roommate Account and your Roommate Account profile page for your use of the Services based upon the personal information you provide us with or that we obtain via a third party as described below. You may not have more than one active Roommate Account at any given time.

You agree to provide accurate, current, and complete information during the registration process and to update such information if necessary to ensure that it is accurate, current and complete. We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your Roommate Account and your access to the Services if you create or allow to exist more than one Roommate Account at a time or if any information provided during the registration process or thereafter proves to be inaccurate, misleading, out of date or incomplete.

We may (but shall not be obliged to) from time to time enable you to create a Roommate Account by logging into your account with an account from certain third party social networking sites, including Facebook (“Social Network Site”), each such account with a Social Network Site being a "Third Party Account".

We may (but shall not be obliged to) from time to time provide functionality within the Services enabling you to link your Roommate Account with one or more Third Party Accounts by either:

Providing your Third Party Account login information to us via the Services; or allowing us to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account.

You represent and promise to us that you are entitled to:

Disclose any Third Party Account login information you disclose to us; and

Grant us access to your Third Party Account, without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without making us liable to pay any fees or making us subject to any usage limitations imposed by the relevant Social Network Site

By granting us access to any Third Party Accounts, you understand that we will access, make available and store (if applicable) any Content that you have provided to and stored in your Third Party Account (“TPA Content”) so that it is available on and through the Services via your Roommate Account and Roommate Account profile page, to the extent permitted under the applicable terms and conditions and settings that govern your use of each Third Party Account. Unless otherwise specified in these Terms, all TPA Content, if any, will be considered to be Member Content for all purposes of these Terms. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, personally identifiable information that you post to your Third Party Accounts will be available on and through your Roommate Account on the Website, Services and Application.

Please note that if a Third Party Account or associated service becomes unavailable or Roommate’s access to such Third Party Account is terminated by the Social Network Site, then TPA Content will no longer be available on and through the Website, Services and Application. You have the ability to disable the connection between your Roommate Account and your Third Party Accounts, at any time, by accessing the “Account” section of the Website and Application. Your relationship with the Social Network Site associated with your Third Party Account is governed solely by your agreement with such Social Network Site. We make no effort to review any TPA Content for any purpose, including for accuracy, legality or non-infringement and we are not responsible for any TPA Content.
    </string>
    <string name="security">
        You are responsible for safeguarding your password. You agree that you will not store your password in any way (whether electronically, on paper, or otherwise) and that you will not disclose your password to any person. Please note that we will never ask for your password by email, phone or in any other way. If anyone claims to be from Roommate and asks for your password you should not provide them with such, but should notify us by email at [insert e-mail address] as soon as possible with copies of any relevant emails you have received or sent and details, including where possible phone numbers of any phone conversations you have had.

You will immediately change your password if at any time you believe someone may have discovered your password. You will immediately notify us if you become aware of any unauthorised use of your Roommate Account, including if you discover that your password has been changed without your consent.

You will take sole responsibility for any activities or actions under your Roommate Account, whether or not you have authorised such activities or actions, except where such activities or actions were authorised by a third party as a result of a failure of our security systems beyond your control.
    </string>
    <string name="user">
        You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for compliance with any and all laws, rules, regulations, and Tax obligations that may apply to your use of the Services and Content as per the applicable laws of the relevant state under the Union of India. In connection with your use of the Services, you may not and you agree that you will not:

violate any laws, rules, regulations of as per the applicable laws of the relevant state under the Union of India, including any order of a court of competent jurisdiction;

use manual or automated software, devices, scripts, robots, other means or processes to access, “scrape”, “crawl” or “spider” any web pages or other services contained in the Services or Content;

use the Services for any commercial or other purposes that are not expressly permitted by these Terms;

copy, store or otherwise access any information contained in/on the Services or Content for purposes not expressly permitted by these Terms;

infringe the rights of any person or entity, including their intellectual property, privacy, publicity or contractual rights;

interfere with or damage our Services, including through the use of viruses, cancel bots, Trojan horses, harmful code, flood pings, denial-of-service attacks, packet or IP spoofing, forged routing or electronic mail address information or similar methods or technology;

use our Services to transmit, distribute, post or submit any information concerning any other person or entity, including photographs of others without their permission, personal contact information or credit, debit, calling card or account numbers;

use our Services in connection with the distribution of unsolicited commercial email ("spam") or Advertisements unrelated to a Property available for rent;

"stalk" or harass any other user of our Services or collect or store any personally identifiable information about any other user other than for purposes of transacting as a Guest, Potential Guest or Host;

offer, as a Host, any Properties that you do not yourself own or have permission to rent out;

offer, as a Host, any Properties which may not be lawfully made available for rent and/or are rented;

offer, as a Host, any Properties which are subject to a mortgage or any other third party rights without first obtaining all necessary consents to do so;

register for more than one Roommate Account or register for a Roommate Account on behalf of an individual other than yourself;

contact a Host for any purpose other than asking a question related to a booking such Host’s Properties or Advertisements;

contact a Guest for any purpose other than asking a question related to a booking; 6.1.16. use the Services to recruit or otherwise solicit any Host or other Member to join third party services or websites that are competitive to Roommate;

impersonate any person or entity, or falsify or otherwise misrepresent yourself or your affiliation with any person or entity;

use automated scripts to collect information or otherwise interact with the Services; 6.1.19. use the Services to find an Host or Guest and then complete a booking of a Property transaction independent of the Services in order to circumvent the obligation to pay any Service Fees related to Roommate’s provision of the Services;

as a Host, submit any Advertisement with false or misleading prices or other information, or submit any Advertisement with a price or other terms that you do not intend to honour;

post, upload, publish, submit or transmit any Content that, in Roommate’s sole judgment; (i) infringe, misappropriate or violate a third party’s patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret, moral rights or other intellectual property rights, or rights of publicity or privacy; (ii) violate, or encourage any conduct that would violate, any applicable law or regulation or would give rise to civil or criminal liability; (iii) is fraudulent, false, misleading or deceptive; (iv) is defamatory, obscene, pornographic, vulgar or offensive; (v) promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group; (vi) is violent or threatening or promotes violence or actions that are threatening to any other person; or (vii) promotes illegal or harmful activities or substances;

Systematically retrieve data or other Content from our Services to create or compile, directly or indirectly, in single or multiple downloads, a collection, compilation, database, directory or the like, whether by manual methods, through the use of bots, crawlers, or spiders, or otherwise;

use, display, mirror or frame the Services, or any individual element within the Services, Roommate’s name, any trademark, logo or other proprietary information, or the layout and design of any page or form contained on a page, without Roommate’s express prior written consent;

access, tamper with, or use non-public areas of the Services, Roommate’s computer systems, or the technical delivery systems of its providers;

attempt to probe, scan, or test the vulnerability of any Roommate system or network or breach any security or authentication measures;

avoid, bypass, remove, deactivate, impair, descramble, or otherwise circumvent any technological measure implemented by Roommate or any of Roommate’s providers or any other third party (including another user) to protect the Services or Collective Content;

forge any TCP/IP packet header or any part of the header information in any email or newsgroup posting, or in any way use the Services or Collective Content to send altered, deceptive or false source-identifying information;

attempt to decipher, decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer any of the software used to provide the Services or Collective Content; or

advocate, encourage, or assist any third party in doing any of the foregoing.

Roommate will have the right to investigate and pursue (possible) violations of any of the above to the fullest extent of the law. Roommate may involve and cooperate with the police and/or prosecuting authorities in prosecuting anyone who violate these Terms. You acknowledge that Roommate has no obligation to monitor your access to or use of the Services or Collective Content or to review or edit any Member Content, but has the right to do so for the purpose of operating the Services, to ensure your compliance with these Terms, or to comply with applicable law or the order of a court of competent jurisdiction, administrative agency or other governmental body. Roommate reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to remove or disable access to any Collective Content that Roommate, at its sole discretion, considers to be objectionable for any reason, in violation of these Terms or otherwise harmful to the Services.

If you interact with another user of the Services who you feel is acting or has acted inappropriately, including anyone who (i) engages in offensive, violent or sexually inappropriate behaviour, (ii) you suspect of committing an offence in relation to you, or (iii) engages in any other disturbing conduct, you should immediately report such person to Roommate at [insert e-mail address]. You are also free to contact the appropriate authorities and then contact Roommate and providing them with the information of the police station you reported the foregoing to and a report number at [insert e-mail address]; provided that your report will not obligate us to take any action beyond that required by law (if any) or cause us to incur any liability to you.
    </string>
    <string name="age">You may only access or use the Services if you are at least 18 years of age and by accessing or using the Services you represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years old. Hosts may specify any minimum age they consider appropriate to rent out their Properties, however unless otherwise specified in any Advertisement for a Property or expressly agreed in writing with an Host, the minimum age to rent a Property is 18</string>
    <string name="privacy">See Roommate’s Privacy Policy for information and notices concerning Roommate’s collection and use of your personal information.</string>
    <string name="intellectual">The Services and Collective Content are protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of The Netherlands and other jurisdictions. You acknowledge and agree that the Services and Collective Content, including all associated intellectual property rights are the exclusive property of Roommate and its licensors. You will not remove, alter or obscure any copyright, trademark, service mark or other proprietary rights notices incorporated in or accompanying the Services or Collective Content. All trademarks, service marks, logos, trade names and any other proprietary designations of Roommate used in/on the Website or Services are trademarks or registered trademarks of Roommate. Any other trademarks, service marks, logos, trade names and any other proprietary designations are the trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective hosts. Roommate respects copyright law and expects you to do the same. It is Roommate’s policy to terminate, if deemed appropriate by Roommate, the Roommate Accounts of Members or other account holders who infringe or are believed to be infringing the rights of copyright holders.</string>
    <string name="content">Subject to your compliance with these Terms, Roommate grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable and non-sub licensable license, to (i) access and view any Roommate Content to which you are permitted access, solely for your personal and non-commercial purposes and (ii) access and view any Member Content to which you are permitted access, solely for your personal and non-commercial purposes. You will not use, copy, adapt, modify, prepare derivative works based upon, distribute, license, sell, transfer, publicly display, publicly perform, transmit, broadcast or otherwise exploit the Services or Collective Content, except as expressly permitted in these Terms. No licenses or rights are granted to you by implication or otherwise under any intellectual property rights owned or controlled by Roommate or its licensors, except for the licenses and rights expressly granted in these Terms.</string>
    <string name="member">We may, in our sole discretion, permit Members to post, upload, publish, submit or transmit Member Content. By making available any Member Content on or through the Website and Services, you hereby grant to Roommate a worldwide, irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, royalty-free license, with the right to sublicense, to use, view, copy, adapt, modify, distribute, license, sell, transfer, publicly display, publicly perform, transmit, stream, broadcast, access, view, and otherwise exploit such Member Content on, through, or by means of the Services or otherwise. Roommate does not claim any hostship rights in/to any such Member Content and nothing in these Terms will be deemed to restrict any rights that you may have to use and exploit any such Member Content. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for all Member Content that you make available through the Services. Accordingly, you represent and warrant that: (i) you either are the sole and exclusive host of all Member Content that you make available through the Services or you have all rights, licenses, consents and releases that are necessary to grant to Roommate the rights in/to such Member Content, as contemplated under these Terms; and (ii) neither the Member Content nor your posting, uploading, publication, submission or transmittal of the Member Content or Roommate’s use of the Member Content (or any portion thereof) on, through or by means of the Services or otherwise will infringe, misappropriate or violate a third party’s patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret, moral rights or other proprietary or intellectual property rights, or rights of publicity or privacy, or result in the violation of any applicable law or regulation. You hereby indemnify and keep indemnified Roommate from any and all claims, and all direct and indirect liabilities, costs, proceedings, damages, losses and expenses (including legal and other professional expenses), awarded against, or incurred or paid by Roommate, as a result of or in connection with any claim arising out of a violation of article 11.2</string>
    <string name="links">The Services contain links to third-party websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that Roommate is not responsible or liable for: (i) the availability or accuracy of such websites or resources; or (ii) the content, products, or services on or available from such websites or resources. Links to such websites or resources do not imply any endorsement by Roommate of such websites or resources or the content, products, or services available from such websites or resources. You acknowledge sole responsibility for and assume all risk arising from your use of any such websites or resources or the content, products or services on or available from such websites or resources.</string>
    <string name="feedback">We welcome and encourage you to provide feedback, comments and suggestions for improvements to the Services (“Feedback”). You may submit Feedback by emailing us at [insert e-mail address] You acknowledge and agree that all Feedback will be the sole and exclusive property of Roommate and you hereby irrevocably assign to Roommate and agree to irrevocably assign to Roommate all of your right, title, and interest in and to all Feedback, including all worldwide patent, copyright, trade secret, moral and other proprietary or intellectual property rights therein. At Roommate’s request and expense, you will execute documents and take such further acts as Roommate may reasonably request to assist Roommate or to acquire, perfect, and maintain its intellectual property rights and other legal protections for the Feedback.r</string>
    <string name="termination">Terminations and Roommate Account Cancellation . We may, in our discretion and without liability to you, with or without cause, with prior notice of 7 days and at any time: (a) terminate these Terms or your access to our Services, and (b) deactivate or cancel your Roommate Account. Upon termination we will promptly pay you any amounts, which we are legally obligated to pay you. In the event Roommate terminates these Terms, or your access to our Services or deactivates or cancels your Roommate Account you will remain liable for all amounts due to be paid by you as per the terms and conditions agreed upon. You may cancel your Roommate Account at any time by sending an email to [insert e-mail address]. Please note that if your Roommate Account is cancelled, we do not have an obligation to delete or return to you any Content you have posted to the Website or otherwise using the Services, including any reviews or Feedback.</string>
    <string name="advertisements">You may create an Advertisement if you are both a Host and a Member. You will be asked a number of questions about the Property to be advertised, including the location, features, amenities, availability, restrictions on use, and pricing. You agree that Advertisements will be distributed and made publicly available via the Services. Once an Host and a Guest have agreed the rent of Property the price and other terms agreed for that rent may only be altered with the consent of both the Host and the Guest. You acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for any and all Advertisements you post. You represent and warrant to us and to all other Members that any Advertisement you post, the booking of a Property advertised in an Advertisement posted by you, and the use by a Guest in accordance with the agreed terms of the rent of any Property advertised in an Advertisement posted by you, you will: not breach any agreements you have entered into with any third parties, including any person who has financed the purchase of the Property; be in compliance with all applicable laws, rules and regulations, including laws relating to the commercial use of Properties and marina regulations. Roommate assumes no responsibility for an Host’s compliance with any applicable laws, rules and regulations and Host hereby indemnifies Roommate of any claims and/or liability, from either a third party or Host arising out of or in connection with the non-compliance of Host with any applicable laws, rules and regulations, including laws, rules and regulations relating to operating permits and mooring permits. Roommate reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to remove or disable access to any Advertisement which Roommate, in its reasonable opinion, considers to be in breach of these Terms or otherwise objectionable or harmful to Roommate’s reputation. You understand and agree that Roommate does not act as an insurer or as an agent with power to enter into contracts for you as a Host. If a Potential Guest requests a booking of your Property, any agreement you enter into with that Potential Guest is between you and the Potential Guest and Roommate is not a party to that agreement. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Roommate serves as the limited agent of the Host for the purpose of accepting payments from Guests on behalf of the Host and is responsible for transmitting such payments to the Host in accordance with the Terms. When you create an Advertisement, you may also choose to include certain requirements which must be met by the Members who are eligible to request a booking of your Property, including requiring Members to have a profile picture or verified phone number, in order to rent your Property. Any Member wishing to rent Properties included in Advertisements with such requirements must meet these requirements. We do not guarantee that any Member claiming to meet any requirements in fact does so and it is your sole responsibility to determine whether or not a Member does meet your requirements. More information on how to set such requirements is available via the “Hosts” section of the Services. If you are a Host, Roommate may make certain tools available to you to help you to make informed decisions about which Members you choose to rent your Property to. You acknowledge and agree that, as a Host, you are solely responsible for your own acts and omissions. Roommate does not represent or guarantee that any person you decide to rent your Property to, whether or not on the basis of any tools made available by Roommate, is qualified or suitable to rent your Property.</string>
    <string name="bookings">If you are a Host and a booking is requested for your Property via the Services, you may be required to either confirm or reject the booking within [insert duration] of when the booking is requested or the booking request may be automatically cancelled. When a booking is requested via the Services, we will share with you (a) the first and last name of the Potential Guest who has requested the booking, and (b) a link to the Potential Guest’s Roommate Account profile page so that you can view the information on that page before confirming or rejecting the booking. If you are unable to confirm or decide to reject a booking of a Property within such 24-hour period, any amounts collected by Roommate for the requested booking will be refunded to the applicable Potential Guest’s credit card and any pre-authorisation of such credit card will be released. When you confirm a booking requested by a Potential Guest, Roommate will send you an email message via the Services confirming such booking, depending on the selections you make via the Services. The fees displayed in each Advertisement are comprised of the Rental Fees and the Service Charges. Where applicable, Tax may be charged in addition to the Rental Fees and Service Charges, such will clearly be stated in the Advertisement. The Rental Fees, Service Charges and applicable Tax are collectively referred to in these Terms as the “Total Fees”. The amounts due and payable by a Guest solely relating to an Host’s Property which are actually collected by Roommate are the “Rental Fees”. Please note that it is the Host and not Roommate which determines the Rental Fees. The Rental Fees may include a cleaning fee or additional costs, at the Host’s discretion. Hosts, not Roommate, are solely responsible for honouring any confirmed bookings and making available any Properties reserved through the Services. If you, as a Guest, choose to enter into a transaction with an Host for the booking of a Property, you agree and understand that you will be entering into a contract with the Host and you agree to accept any terms, conditions, rules and restrictions associated with such Property imposed by the Host, all of which will be notified to you before you are required to commit to that contract. You acknowledge and agree that you, and not Roommate, will be responsible for performing the obligations of any such contracts, that Roommate is not a party to such agreements, and that, with the exception of its obligations hereunder to pay Rental Fees and Late Charges to the applicable Host, Roommate disclaims all liability arising from or related to any such agreements. You acknowledge and agree that, notwithstanding the fact that Roommate is not a party to the agreement between you and the Host, Roommate acts as the Host’s payment agent for the limited purpose of accepting payments from you on behalf of the Host. Upon your payment of amounts to Roommate which are due to the Host, your payment obligation to the Host for such amounts is fulfilled, and Roommate is responsible for remitting such amounts, less Roommate’s Service Fees, to the Host as per the payment terms agreed by and between Roommate and the Host. In the event that Roommate does not remit any such amounts to Host, such Host will have recourse for such amounts only against Roommate. You, the Guest, agree to pay Roommate the Rental Fees and Late Charges for any booking requested in connection with your Roommate Account if such requested bookings are confirmed by the applicable Host. In order to establish a booking pending the applicable Host’s confirmation of your requested booking, you understand and agree that Roommate, on behalf of the Host, reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to (i) obtain a pre-authorisation via your credit card/debit card/post dated cheque/net banking for the Rental Fees or (ii) charge your credit card/debit card a nominal amount, not to exceed [insert amount] to verify your card. Once Roommate receives confirmation of your booking from the applicable Host, Roommate will collect the Rental Fees and Late Charges in accordance with these Terms and the pricing terms set forth in the applicable Listing. Please note that Roommate cannot control any fees that may be charged to a Guest by his or her bank related to Roommate’s collection of the Rental Fees or Late Charges, and Roommate disclaims all liability in this regard. In connection with a requested booking, a Prospective Guest will be asked to provide customary billing information such as name, billing address and credit card information either to Roommate or its third party payment processor. You agree to pay Roommate for Rental Fees and Late Charges for any confirmed bookings made in connection with your Roommate Account in accordance with these Terms by one of the methods described on the Website –e.g. by credit card/debit card/ post dated cheque/net banking. You hereby authorize the collection of such amounts by charging the credit card provided as part of requesting the booking, either directly by Roommate or indirectly, via a third party online payment processor or by one of the payment methods described on the Services. You also authorize Roommate to charge your credit card or use any of the post dated cheques provided as per the terms and conditions agreed between the Guest and the Host in the event of damage caused to a Property as contemplated in paragraph 17. If you are directed to Roommate’s third party payment processor, you may be subject to terms and conditions governing use of that third party’s service and that third party’s personal information collection practices. Please review such terms and conditions and, if applicable their privacy policy, before using the services.Once your confirmed booking transaction is complete you will receive a confirmation email summarizing your confirmed booking.</string>
    <string name="deposits">A security deposit will be specified in every Advertisement (“Security Deposit”). For all Security Deposits included in an Advertisement for a confirmed booking of a Property, Roommate will, in its capacity as the payment agent of the Host, use its reasonable endeavours to obtain a pre-authorisation of the Guest’s credit card in the amount the Host determines for the Security Deposit within a reasonable time prior to the commencement of the Guest’s rent of the Property. Roommate will also use its reasonable endeavours to address Hosts’ requests and claims related to such Security Deposits, but Roommate is not responsible for administering or accepting any claims by Hosts related to Security Deposits, and disclaims any and all liability in this regard. 17.2. A Security Deposit may be applied towards, and a Guest’s credit card charged up to the amount of the Security Deposit for: 17.2.1. the cost of making good any damage to a Property for which a Guest is responsible and which is not covered by the Insurance Policy, including damage up to the amount of any excess on the Insurance Policy for the respective Property; 17.2.2. any Late Charges payable by a Guest. A Guest’s liability for damage to a Property is not limited to the amount of the Security Deposit provided by the Guest. See paragraph 25 below for further terms in relation to damage to Properties.</string>
    <string name="charges">In consideration for providing the Services, Roommate charges a onetime listing charge of Rs. 5000/-(rupees five thousand) and additional service fees to Hosts (“Service Fees”). Service Fees are based upon a percentage of the amount of Rental Fees and Late Charges (if any), excluding any Tax. Where applicable, Goods and Service Tax and any other applicable Tax may also be charged to Host in addition to the Service Fees. Service Fees are deducted from the Rental Fees before remitting the Rental Fees to the Host, within [insert time/duration] of when the Guest checks in the applicable Property at the end of the Actual Rental Period. Balances will be remitted by Roommate to Hosts by direct credit transfer or other payment methods described on the Services. More information on Services Fees can be found at https://roommate.techmihirnaik.in/. Except as otherwise provided herein, Service Fees are non-refundable. For Basic Subscriptions all bookings will be charged with a 10% Service Fee (commission) by Roommate.</string>
    <string name="cancellation">If, as a guest, you cancel your requested booking before the requested booking is confirmed by an Host, Roommate will cancel any pre-authorization to your credit card and/or refund any nominal amounts charged to your credit card in connection with the requested booking within a commercially reasonable time. If, as a Guest, you wish to cancel a confirmed booking made via the Services, the cancellation policy of the Host contained in the applicable Advertisement will apply to such cancellation. The host has the choice of Very Strict, Strict, Medium or Flexible cancellation policy:

VERY STRICT If you cancel the booking -up to 10 days before check-in you will be not be charged a cancellation amount -up to five days before check-in you will be charged for 50% of the booking amount -up to two days before check-in you will be charged for 100%of the booking amount.

STRICT If you cancel the booking -up to six weeks before check-in you will be charged for 30% of the booking amount -up to four weeks before check-in you will be charged for 50% of the booking amount -up to two weeks before check-in you will be charged for 80% of the booking amount –after two weeks before check-in you will be charged for 100% of the booking amount.

MEDIUM If you cancel the booking -up to six weeks before check-in you will be charged for 25% of the booking amount -up to four weeks before check-in you will be charged for 40% of the booking amount -up to one week before check-in you will be charged for 60% of the booking amount –after one weeks before check-in you will be charged for 100% of the booking amount.

FLEXIBLE If you cancel the booking -up to one month before check-in you will be charged for 20% of the booking amount -up to two weeks before check-in you will be charged for 20% of the booking amount -up to 7 days before check-in you will be charged for 20% of the booking amount -up to 24 hours before check-in you will be charged for 50% of the booking amount -on the day of check-in you will be charged for 75% of the booking amount.[further input required]

If there is no cancellation policy shown in the hosts’ advertisement the general policy will count as: "Very Strict". The reservation is officially cancelled when the Guest sends an email to [insert e-mail address] and receives a confirmation. In case of complaints from any party, Roommate has the final word in any dispute in its sole discretion. Cancellation policies may be superseded by the safety cancellations, Guest Refund Policy (as below defined), or Extenuating Circumstances (as below defined). All users are encouraged to check these carefully by reading the following exceptions.

The Host is not allowed to cancel a confirmed booking unless there is an event of force majeure. In the event the Host decides to cancel a confirmed booking otherwise than a force majeure event, a penalty of the cancellation charge and refund amount and GST will be charged by Roommate from the host. For the purposes of this agreement, "Event of Force Majeure" means an event including but not limited to:

1 act of God (such as, but not limited to, fires, explosions, earthquakes, drought, tidal waves and floods);

war, hostilities (whether war be declared or not), invasion, act of foreign enemies, mobilisation, requisition, or embargo;

rebellion, revolution, insurrection, or military or usurped power, or civil war;

contamination by radio-activity from any nuclear fuel, or from any nuclear waste from the combustion of nuclear fuel, radio-active toxic explosive, or other hazardous properties of any explosive nuclear assembly or nuclear component of such assembly;

riot, commotion, strikes, go slows, lock outs or disorder, unless solely restricted to employees of the Supplier or of his Subcontractors; or

acts or threats of terrorism. Unless Roommate has offered alternative accommodation the Host will endeavor to make alternative arrangements of equal or better quality at the cost of the Host and in case there is no Accommodation available On arrival the Host will: (i) find suitable alternative accommodation of the same or better standard as compared to the reservation guaranteed by the Guest Accommodation; (ii) offer free private transport to the alternative accommodation for the Guest, and (iii) To compensate Roommate and / or compensate the Guest for all costs and expenses reasonably incurred or suffered by Roommate and / or the Guest (such as cost of alternative accommodation, transportation, telephone charges)as a consequence of the initial cancellation. Any amount and penalties charged by Roommate in such case will be paid within [insert duration] of receipt of the invoice. The Host hereby agrees that the amount will be automatically charged from the Host’s credit card on file.</string>
    <string name="appoinment">Each Host hereby appoints Roommate as the Hosts limited agent solely for the purpose of collecting payments made by Guests on behalf of the Host and forwarding such payments to Host, minus the applicable Service Fees. Each Host agrees that payment of Rental Fees made by a Guest to Roommate shall be considered the same as a payment made directly to the Host and the Host will make the Property available to a Guest in the agreed upon manner as if the Host has received the Rental Charges. Each Host agrees that Roommate may, in accordance with the cancellation policy stated in the terms and conditions and reflected in the relevant Advertisement, (i) permit the Guest to cancel the booking and (ii) refund to the Guest that portion of the Rental Fees specified in the cancellation policy. In accepting appointment as the limited authorised agent of the Host, Roommate assumes no liability for any acts or omissions of the Host.</string>
    <string name="prerent">Prior to the commencement of the Agreed Rental Period, the Guest may inspect the Property in the company of the Host or the Host’s representative to assess the condition of the Property and to satisfy the Guest that the Property is as described in the Advertisement the Guest responded to or is otherwise in such condition as has been agreed between the Host and the Guest. Acceptance of the Property by the Guest shall be evidence that the Property is in a satisfactory condition in accordance with the terms of the contract between the Guest and the Host. If the Guest does not accept delivery of the Property within three hours from the start of the Agreed Rental Period and has not notified the Host of Guest’s intention to accept delivery later during the Agreed Rental Period, the Host may terminate the Rent and shall be entitled to payment of such sums as would be payable under the cancellation policy of the Host contained in the applicable Advertisement in the event of a cancellation by the Guest on the day the Agreed Rental Period was due to commence. If the Host is able to re-rent the Property for any part of the original Agreed Rental Period, the Host shall give credit to the original Guest for any sums received for such re-hire, less any additional costs incurred by the Host</string>
    <string name="host">to handover the Property to the Guest: at the start of the Agreed Rental Period, failing which (i) if the delay is up to 25% of the Agreed Rental Period, the Host’s liability shall be limited to a pro rata refund of the Rental Fees, and (ii) if the delay is 25% or more of the Agreed Rental Period the Guest shall be entitled to terminate the Rent and receive a refund of all sums paid and shall have no liability to the Host to pay any Rental Fees or Late Charges and shall be entitled to the release of the Guest’s Security Deposit; in the condition described in the Advertisement the Guest responded to or in such other condition as agreed with the Guest; in the event of a Guest terminating the Rent under paragraph 24.1.1, to compensate the Guest for any non-refundable travel or accommodation expenses reasonably incurred in connection with, or anticipation of, the Rent, provided that (i) the Host shall have no liability to the Guest in respect of any other consequential loss or loss of use or enjoyment of the Property, and (ii) the Host’s liability to the Guest for any breach of contract entitling the Guest to terminate the Rent under paragraph 24.1.1 shall not exceed [insert percentage] of the Rental Fees agreed for the Rent; to permit the Guest to use the Property in accordance with these Terms for the Agreed Rental Period, provided that the Host does not warrant or represent that the Property is suitable for any particular purpose unless expressly stated in the Advertisement the Guest responded to or as otherwise agreed in writing by the Host;</string>
    <string name="scope">If you choose to use the Services, you do so at your own risk. You acknowledge and agree that Roommate does not have an obligation to conduct background checks on any Member, including (Potential) Guests and Hosts, but, at its sole discretion, may conduct such background checks. The Services and/or Collective Content are provided “as is”, without warranty of any kind, either express or implied. Without limiting the foregoing, Roommate explicitly disclaims any warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of any kind, and any warranties arising out of or in the course of dealing or usage of trade. Roommate makes no warranty that the Services and/or Collective Content, including the Advertisements or any Properties, will meet your requirements or be available on an uninterrupted, secure, or error-free basis. Roommate makes no warranty regarding the quality of any Advertisements, Properties, or the Services or Member Content or the accuracy, timeliness, truthfulness, completeness or reliability of any Member Content. No advice or information, whether oral or written, obtained from Roommate or through the Services or Collective Content, will create any warranty not expressly made herein, unless expressly made in any such advice or information. You are solely responsible for all of your communications and interactions with other users of the Services and with other persons with whom you communicate or interact as a result of your use of the Services, including any Hosts or (Potential) Guests. You understand that Roommate does not make any attempt to verify the statements of users on/of the Website or Services or to review or inspect any Properties. Roommate makes no representations or warranties as to the conduct of users of the Website, Application or Services or their compatibility with any current or future users of the Website, Application or Services. You agree to take reasonable precautions in all communications and interactions with other users of the Website, Application or Services and with other persons with whom you communicate or interact as a result of your use of the Website, Application or Services, including (Potential) Guests and Hosts, particularly if you decide to meet offline or in person regardless of whether such meetings are organized by Roommate. Notwithstanding Roommate’s appointment as the limited agent of the Hosts for the purpose of accepting payments from Guests on behalf of the Hosts, Roommate explicitly disclaims any and all liability for any act or omission of any Potential Guest, Guest or other third party.</string>
    <string name="limitations">You acknowledge and agree that, the entire risk arising out of or in connection with your access to and use of the Services and Collective Content, your Advertisement or booking of and use of any Properties via the Services, and any contact you have with other users of the Services whether in person or online remains with you. Neither Roommate nor any other party involved in creating, producing, or delivering the Service and/or Collective Content will be liable for any direct or indirect damages, including lost profits, loss of data or loss of goodwill, service interruption, computer damage or system failure or the cost of substitute products or services, or for any damages for personal or bodily injury or emotional distress arising out of or in connection with these Terms, from the use of or inability to use the Services and/or Collective Content, from any communications, interactions or meetings with other users of the Services or other persons with whom you communicate or interact as a result of your use of the Services, or from your Advertisement, booking, or use of any Property via the Services, whether based on warranty, contract, unlawful act, product liability or any other legal basis, and whether or not Roommate has been informed of the possibility of such damage, even if a limited remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose. Except for our obligations to pay amounts due by Guests to Hosts pursuant to these Terms, in no event will Roommate’s aggregate liability arising out of or in connection with these Terms and your use of the Services including from your Advertisement, booking or use of any Property via the Services, or from the use of or inability to use the Services, or Collective Content and in connection with any Property or interactions with any other Members, exceed the amounts you have paid for bookings via the Website, Application and Services as a guest in the twelve (12) month period prior to the event giving rise to the liability, or if you are an Host, the amounts paid by Roommate to you in the twelve (12) month period prior to the event giving rise to the liability, , if no such payments have been made, as applicable. The limitations of damages set forth above are fundamental elements of the basis of the contract between Roommate and you. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, so the above limitation may not apply to you if that is the case in your jurisdiction.</string>
    <string name="indemni">You agree to release, defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Roommate and all companies in its group of companies including parent companies, and their officers, directors, employees and agents, from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, losses, and expenses, including reasonable legal and other professional fees, arising out of or in any way connected with (a) your access to or use of the Services and/or Collective Content or your violation of these Terms; (b) your Member Content; © your (i) interaction with any Member, (ii) booking, rent or use of a Property, (iii) creation of an Advertisement or (iv) the use, condition or rent of a Property by you, including any injuries, losses, or damages (compensatory, direct, incidental, consequential or otherwise) of any kind arising in connection with or as a result of a rent , booking or use of a Property.</string>
    <string name="intro">Roommate recognizes the importance of privacy of its users and also of maintaining confidentiality of the information provided by its users as a responsible data controller and data processor. This Privacy Policy provides for the practices for handling and securing users Personal Information (defined hereunder) by Roommate and its subsidiaries and affiliates. This Privacy Policy is applicable to any person (‘User’) who purchases, intends to purchase, or inquire about any product(s) or service(s) made available by Roommate through any of Roommate customer interface channels including its website, mobile site, mobile app &amp; offline channels including call centers and offices (collectively referred herein as "Sales Channels"). For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, wherever the context so requires "you" or "your" shall mean User and the term "we", "us", "our" shall mean Roommate. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, Website means the website(s), mobile site(s) and mobile app(s). By using or accessing the Website or other Sales Channels, the User hereby agrees with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the contents herein. If you disagree with this Privacy Policy please do not use or access our Website or other Sales Channels. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any website(s), mobile sites and mobile apps of third parties, even if their websites/products are linked to our Website. User should take note that information and privacy practices of Roommate business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which Roommate provides hyperlink(s), may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, it is recommended that you review the privacy statements and policies of any such third parties with whom they interact. This Privacy Policy is an integral part of your User Agreement with Roommate and all capitalized terms used, but not otherwise defined herein, shall have the respective meanings as ascribed to them in the User Agreement.</string>
    <string name="b_user">Please note that the data shared with Roommate shall be primarily processed in India and such other jurisdictions where a third party engaged by Roommate may process the data on its behalf. By agreeing to this policy, you are providing Roommate with your explicit consent to process your personal information for the purpose(s) defined in this policy. The data protection regulations in India or such other jurisdictions mentioned above may differ from those of your country of residence. If you have any concerns in the processing your data and wish to withdraw your consent, you may do so by writing to the following email id: Hello@roommate.techmihirnaik.in However, if such processing of data is essential for us to be able to provide a service(s) to you, then we may not be able to serve or confirm your bookings after your withdrawal of consent. For instance, if you make a booking (PG/Flat/Hostel), then certain personal information of yours like contact details, gender, dietary preferences, choice of room, any medical condition which may require specific attention or facility etc. may have to be shared by us with our vendors, and they may further process this information for making suitable arrangements for you during your trip. A withdrawal of consent by you for us to process your information may: Severely inhibit our ability to serve you properly and in such case, we may have to refuse the booking altogether, or unreasonably restrict us to service your booking (if a booking is already made) which may further affect your trip or may compel us to cancel your booking.</string>
    <string name="c_type">The information as detailed below is collected for us to be able to provide the services chosen by you and also to fulfill our legal obligations as well as our obligations towards third parties as per our User Agreement. "Personal Information" of User shall include the information shared by the User and collected by us for the following purposes: Registration on the Website: Information which you provide while subscribing to or registering on the Website, including but not limited to information about your personal identity such as name, gender, marital status, religion, age etc., your contact details such as your email address, postal addresses, telephone (mobile or otherwise) and/or fax numbers. The information may also include information such as your banking details (including credit/debit card) and any other information relating to your income and/or lifestyle; billing information, payment history etc. (as shared by you). Other information: We many also collect some other information and documents including but not limited to: Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities, buying behavior. Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services. Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc. Data available in public domain or received from any third party including social media channels, including but not limited to personal or non-personal information from your linked social media channels (like name, email address, friend list, profile pictures or any other information that is permitted to be received as per your account settings) as a part of your account information. Information pertaining any other traveler(s) for who you make a booking through your registered Roommate account. In such case, you must confirm and represent that each of the other traveler(s) for whom a booking has been made, has agreed to have the information shared by you disclosed to us and further be shared by us with the concerned service provider(s). If you request Roommate to provide visa related services, then copies of your passport, bank statements, originals of the filled in application forms, photographs, and any other information which may be required by the respective embassy to process your visa application. In case you opt for contactless check-in at Hotels, then copies of your government identification like aadhar, driving license, election card etc., Self-declaration and any other information like date of birth, destination/origin of travel and place of residence that may be required by the concerned Hotel to honor your hotel booking. Your Covid-19 Vaccination status and certificate in case you wish to avail any service for provision of which such Covid-19 vaccination related information is required or want to access your vaccination certificate at a later stage for travel related or any other purpose. Roommates will never process the beneficiary id and other id details contained in the vaccination certificate. Such information shall be strictly used for the aforesaid specified &amp; lawful purpose only. Users further understand that Roommate may share this information with the end service provider or any other third party for provision and facilitation of the desired booking. Roommate will always redact all/any sensitive &amp; confidential information contained in the vaccination certificate, passbook, bank statement or any other identity card submitted for the purpose of availing a service, promotional offer or booking a product on the Website. In case a User does not wish to provide this information or opts for deletion of the information already provided, Roommate may not be able to process the desired booking request.Roommate will never share any of the above information collected including PAN card details, Vaccination status &amp; certificate , Pa.</string>
    <string name="d_how">The Personal Information collected maybe used in the following manner: While making a booking: While making a booking, we may use Personal Information including, payment details which include cardholder name, credit/debit card number (in encrypted form) with expiration date, banking details, wallet details etc. as shared and allowed to be stored by you. We may also use the information of travelers list as available in or linked with your account. This information is presented to the User at the time of making a booking to enable you to complete your bookings expeditiously. We may also use your Personal Information for several reasons including but not limited to: confirm your reservations with respective service providers; keep you informed of the transaction status; send booking confirmations either via sms or Whatsapp or any other messaging service; send any updates or changes to your booking(s); allow our customer service to contact you, if necessary; customize the content of our website, mobile site and mobile app; request for reviews of products or services or any other improvements; send verification message(s) or email(s); Validate/authenticate your account and to prevent any misuse or abuse. contact you on your birthday/anniversary to offer a special gift or offer.</string>
    <string name="surveys">We value opinions and comments from our Users and frequently conduct surveys, both online and offline. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information received is aggregated, and used to make improvements to Website, other Sales Channels, services and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for members based on the results of the surveys. Identity of the survey participants is anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.</string>
    <string name="marketing">Marketing promotions, research and programs help us to identify your preferences, develop programs and improve user experience. Personal Information collected by us for such activities may include contact information and survey questions. We use such Personal Information to notify contest winners and survey information to develop promotions and product improvements. As a registered User, you will also occasionally receive updates from us about fare sales in your area, special offers, new services, other noteworthy items (like savings and benefits on airfares, hotel reservations, holiday packages, car rentals and other travel services) and marketing programs. In addition, you may look forward to receiving periodic marketing emails, newsletters and exclusive promotions offering special deals. From time to time we may add or enhance services available on the Website. To the extent these services are provided, and used by you, we will use the Personal Information you provide to facilitate the service(s) requested. For example, if you email us with a question, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such Personal Information to assist us in making the Website the better and easier to use for our Users. Roommate may from time to time launch reward programs by way of which users may stand to win travel related rewards or other rewards. We may use your Personal Information to enroll you in the rewards program and status of the same will be visible each time you log in to the Website. Depending on the reward program, each time you win a reward, Roommate may share your Personal Information with a third party that will be responsible for fulfilling the reward to you. You may however choose to opt out of such reward programs by writing to us. For various purposes such as fraud detection, offering bookings on credit etc., we at times may verify information of customers on selective basis, including their credit information.</string>
    <string name="e_how">Roommate will retain your Personal Information on its servers for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes listed in this policy. In some circumstances we may retain your Personal Information for longer periods of time, for instance where we are required to do so in accordance with any legal, regulatory, tax or accounting requirements. Where your personal data is no longer required we will ensure it is either securely deleted or stored in a way which means it will no longer be used by the business.</string>
    <string name="cookies">Cookies Roommate uses cookies to personalize your experience on the Website and the advertisements that maybe displayed. Roommate\'s use of cookies is similar to that of any other reputable online companies. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your device\'s hard drive. Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently. Cookies also allow ease of access, by logging you in without having to type your login name each time (only your password is needed); we may also use such cookies to display any advertisement(s) to you while you are on the Website or to send you offers (or similar emails – provided you have not opted out of receiving such emails) focusing on destinations which may be of your interest. A cookie may also be placed by our advertising servers, or third party advertising companies. Such cookies are used for purposes of tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on any website, and also to use aggregated statistics about your visits to the Website in order to provide advertisements in the Website or any other website about services that may be of potential interest to you. The third party advertising companies or advertisement providers may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of the advertisements. All such information is anonymous. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is an industry standard technology and is used by all major websites. They may use this anonymous information about your visits to the Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. No Personal Information is collected during this process. The information so collected during this process, is anonymous, and does not link online actions to a User. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Of course, by changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. ROOMMATE supports your right to block any unwanted internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites. However, blocking ROOMMATE cookies may disable certain features on the Website, and may hinder an otherwise seamless experience to purchase or use certain services available on the Website. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain websites while permitting cookies from websites you trust. Automatic Logging of Session Data: Each time you access the Website your session data gets logged. Session data may consist of various aspects like the IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the User while on the Website. We collect session data because it helps us analyze User’s choices, browsing pattern including the frequency of visits and duration for which a User is logged on. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. The aforesaid information cannot identify any User personally. However, it may be possible to determine a User\'s Internet Service Provider (ISP), and the approximate geographic location of User\'s point of connectivity through the above session data.</string>
    <string name="g_with">Service Providers and suppliers: Your information shall be shared with the end service providers like airlines, hotels, bus service providers, cab rental, railways or any other suppliers who are responsible for fulfilling your booking. You may note that while making a booking with ROOMMATE you authorize us to share your information with the said service providers and suppliers. It is pertinent to note that ROOMMATE does not authorize the end service provider to use your information for any other purpose(s) except as may be for fulfilling their part of service. However, how the said service providers/suppliers use the information shared with them is beyond the purview and control of ROOMMATE as they process Personal Information as independent data controllers, and hence we cannot be made accountable for the same. You are therefore advised to review the privacy policies of the respective service provider or supplier whose services you choose to avail. ROOMMATE does not sell or rent individual customer names or other Personal Information of Users to third parties except sharing of such information with our business / alliance partners or vendors who are engaged by us for providing various referral services and for sharing promotional and other benefits to our customers from time to time basis their booking history with us.</string>
    <string name="company">In the interests of improving personalization and service efficiency, we may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your Personal Information with our affiliate or associate entities. . This will enable us to provide you with information about various products and services, both leisure- and travel-related, which might interest you; or help us address your questions and requests in relation to your bookings. If the assets of ROOMMATE are acquired, our customer information may also be transferred to the acquirer depending upon the nature of such acquisition. In addition, as part of business expansion/development/restructuring or for any other reason whatsoever, if we decide to sell/transfer/assign our business, any part thereof, any of our subsidiaries or any business units, then as part of such restructuring exercise customer information including the Personal Information collected herein shall be transferred accordingly.</string>
    <string name="patners">We may also share certain filtered Personal Information to our corporate affiliates or business partners who may contact the customers to offer certain products or services, which may include free or paid products / services, which will enable the customer to have better travel experience or to avail certain benefits specially made for ROOMMATE customers. Examples of POSTICA for courier, EIKARICA for e commerce, and many more. If you choose to avail any such services offered by our business partners, the services so availed will be governed by the privacy policy of the respective service provider. Roommate may share your Personal Information to third party that ROOMMATE may engage to perform certain tasks on its behalf, including but not limited to payment processing, data hosting, and data processing platforms. We use non-identifiable Personal Information of Users in aggregate or anonymized form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analysis of the collective characteristics and behavior of our customers and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the Website. We may provide anonymous statistical information based on this data to suppliers, advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business partners. We may also use such aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their websites. Any Personal Information which we collect and which we may use in an aggregated format is our property. We may use it, in our sole discretion and without any compensation to you, for any legitimate purpose including without limitation the commercial sale thereof to third parties. Occasionally,Roommate will hire a third party for market research, surveys etc. and will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. The information (including aggregate cookie and tracking information) we provide to such third parties, alliance partners, or vendors are protected by confidentiality agreements and such information is to be used solely for completing the specific project, and in compliance with the applicable regulations.</string>
    <string name="disclosure">In addition to the circumstances described above, Roommate may disclose User\'s Personal Information if required to do so: by law, required by any enforcement authority for investigation, by court order or in reference to any legal process; to conduct our business; for regulatory, internal compliance and audit exercise(s) to secure our systems; or to enforce or protect our rights or properties of ROOMMATE or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers or when we have reason to believe that disclosing Personal Information of User(s) is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. Such disclosure and storage may take place without your knowledge. In that case, we shall not be liable to you or any third party for any damages however arising from such disclosure and storage</string>
    <string name="h_user">Roommate provides an option to its users to post their experiences by way of reviews, ratings and general poll questions. The customers also have an option of posting questions w.r.t a service offered by Roommate or post answers to questions raised by other users. We may also hire a third party to contact you and gather feedback about your recent booking with ROOMMATE. Though the participation in the feedback process is purely optional, you may still receive emails, notifications (app, sms, Whatsapp or any other messaging service) for you to share your review(s), answer questions posted by other users. The reviews may be written or in a video format. The reviews written or posted may also be visible on other travel or travel related platforms.</string>
    <string name="review"><![CDATA[Crowd Source Data Collection (poll questions). Each User who posts review or ratings, Q&A, photographs shall have a profile, which other Users will be able to access. Other Users may be able to view the number of trips, reviews written, questions asked and answered and photographs posted.]]></string>
    <string name="i_how">You will occasionally receive e-mail updates from us about fare sales in your area, special offers, new Roommate services, and other noteworthy items. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. If you wish not to receive them, please click on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the instructions in each e-mail message.</string>
    <string name="j_permission">When the Roommate app is installed on your phone or tablet, a list of permissions appear and are needed for the app to function effectively. There is no option to customize the list. The permissions that ROOMMATE requires and the data that shall be accessed and its use is as below:

Android permissions: Device &amp; App history: We need your device permission to get information about your device, like OS (operating system) name, OS version, mobile network, hardware model, unique device identifier, preferred language, etc. Basis these inputs, we intend to optimize your travel booking experience, use OS specific capabilities to drive great in-funnel experiences using components of device’s OS, etc.

Identity: This permission enables us to know about details of your account(s) on your mobile device. We use this info to auto-fill your email ID’s and provide a typing free in-funnel experience. It helps us map email ID’s to a particular user to give you the benefit of exclusive travel offers, wallet cash-backs, etc. It also allows facilitating your Facebook and Google+ login.

Location: This permission enables us to give you the benefit of location specific deals and provide you a personalized in-funnel experience. When you launch goibibo app to make a travel booking, we auto-detect your location so that your nearest airport or city is auto-filled. We also require this permission to recommend you nearest hotels in case you are running late and want to make a quick last minute booking for the nearest hotel. Your options are personalized basis your locations. For international travel, this enables us to determine your time zone and provide information accordingly

SMS: If you allow us to access your SMS, we read your SMS to autofill or prepopulate OTP while making a transaction and to validate your mobile number. This provides you a seamless purchase experience while making a booking and you don’t need to move out of the app to read the SMS and then enter it in the app. SMS is also used to show a customer upcoming PNR status confirmations.

Phone: The app requires access to make phone calls so that you can make phone calls to hotels, airlines and our customer contact centers directly through the app. Contacts: If you allow us to access your contacts, it enables us to provide a lot of social features to you such as sharing your hotel/ flight/ holidays with your friends, inviting your friends to try our app, send across referral links to your friends, etc. We may also use this information to make recommendations for hotels where your friends have stayed. This information will be stored on our servers and synced from your phone.

Photo/ Media/ Files:The libraries in the app use these permissions to allow map data to be saved to your phones external storage, like SD cards. By saving map data locally, your phone doesnt need to re-download the same map data every time you use the app. This provides you a seamless Map based Hotel selection experience, even on low bandwidth network.

Wi-Fi connection information: When you allow us the permission to detect your Wi-Fi connection, we optimize your experience such as more detailing on maps, better image loading, more hotel/ flights/ package options to choose from, etc. Device ID &amp; Call information: This permission is used to detect your Android ID through which we can uniquely identify users. It also lets us know your contact details using which we pre-populate specific fields to ensure a seamless booking experience.

Calendar: This permission enables us to put your travel plan on your calendar.

IOS Permissions:

Notifications: If you opt in for notifications, it enables us to send across exclusive deals, promotional offers, travel related updates, etc. on your device. If you do not opt for this, updates for your travel like PNR status, booking confirmation, refund (in case of cancellation), etc. will be sent through SMS.

Contacts: If you opt in for contacts permission, it enables us to provide a lot of social features to you such as sharing your hotel/ flight/ holidays with your friends, inviting your friends to try our app, send across referral links to your friends, etc. We will also use this information to make recommendations for hotels where your friends have stayed. This information will be stored on our servers and synced from your phone.

Location: This permission enables us to give you the benefit of location specific deals and provide you a personalized in-funnel experience. When you launch our app to make a travel booking, we auto-detect your location so that your nearest Airport or City is auto-filled. We require this permission to recommend your nearest hotels in case you are running late and want to make a quick last minute booking for the nearest hotel. Your options are personalized basis your locations. For international travel, this enables us to determine your time zone and provide information accordingly.

Siri: Permission to access “Siri” is required to enable you to make cab bookings through “Siri” on the goibibo app. Camera &amp; Photo Library: The access to your camera is required to enable you to be able to click, review and upload your profile photo. Alternately, access to your photo library is required for to enable you to upload an existing photograph as a profile picture.</string>
    <string name="k_how">All payments on the Website are secured. This means all Personal Information you provide is transmitted using TLS (Transport Layer Security) encryption. TSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.</string>
    <string name="l_with">You may withdraw your consent to submit any or all Personal Information or decline to provide any permissions on its Website as covered above at any time. In case, you choose to do so then your access to the Website may be limited, or we might not be able to provide the services to you. You may withdraw your consent by sending an email to roommate@techmihirnaik.in</string>
    <string name="m_your">You may access your Personal Information from your user account with ROOMMATE. You may also correct your personal information or delete such information (except some mandatory fields) from your user account directly. If you dont have such a user account, then you write to hello@roommate.techmihirnaik.in</string>
    <string name="o">We reserve the rights to revise the Privacy Policy from time to time to suit various legal, business and customer requirement. We will duly notify the users as may be necessary. You may always submit concerns regarding this Privacy Policy via email to us at hello@roommate.techmihirnaik.in. Roommate shall endeavor to respond to all reasonable concerns and inquires.</string>
</resources>






